bit of natural justice (only type we're going to get) as Halfpenny misses that one. #WALvSCO
I think once they're out the response time of the average user will drop and give you some natural load balancing :)
Broken #Sleep May Be Natural: uninterrupted 8 hours could be recent and side effect of artificial lighting. http://t.co/qpCn5yrD
@RugbyScotland Not to do with having to agree, suggestions/ change put forward natural reaction is focus problems & why it wont work
@tattyheaded i'd go further; I'd happily swap being killed, in exchange for being pissed on after I die of natural causes. If sum1 offered.
@oscargodson @polotek @wycats Yet languages borrow (both natural and programming), and the real inspiration for block-lambdas is Smalltalk.
@MyShowBizFam @JayPose @valentinapere31 Youve managed to get a broud of very photogenic children. And so natural on camera.
I've never rooted for the Steelers in my natural lifetime, but for the love of all that's holy PLEASE STEELERS BEAT DENVER... :3
I'm watching Natural City http://t.co/8YyEdqU3 @GetGlue #NaturalCity
You have been pulled out of your natural habitat today, yet ar... More for Scorpio http://twittascope.com/?sign=8
@damedametuna -of Tsuna's hip, a soft, low moan escaping; hips rolling slowly up into the other, entirely responsive to his touch, natural/
@ShigureSoenRyu -already seems so natural and relaxed, as if they've been this close for years even;rolls his hips, some of the nervousness-
@SweatyMikeY @A_mar71 @girlslovenerds @bmason270 u all might want to look@ CLA 500 by Nutrilite. reduce fat,retain lean muscle. all-natural
@guntotin Why does everyone get so flustered over sex talk? It's a natural thing, haha. /so very, very amused/
@skullfromhell @damedametuna @fistsforgodI Don't be such a kid, kora. It's a perfectly natural subject. Like the weather.
A blz natural é melhor que a "artificial" RT @KamilaRios: @Hugorkut @debalaguera @tiagonazare A beleza natural é imbativel. Sei não viu...
Claro que tem casos que é necessário. RT @KamilaRios: @Hugorkut @debalaguera @tiagonazare A beleza natural é imbativel. Sei não viu...
@Hugorkut @debalaguera @tiagonazare A beleza natural é imbativel. Sei não viu...
100% de acordo! RT @debalaguera: Viram meninas?! RT @tiagonazare Mulher não precisa se maquiar muito... A beleza natural é imbativel.
Viram meninas?! RT @tiagonazare Mulher não precisa se maquiar muito... A beleza natural é imbativel.
@tothechest @blimrock JOTENT - jerking off to enermous natural tits
Reestablishing the Natural Order : v2 http://wp.me/pfkIG-20
@RubenPerot jajaja Nada de rimel ! Todo natural ! Preguntale a @PaulaBertol...
@GarethCliff @DJFreshSA Why are you 2 not in charge! It is natural selection. Same reason ppl should be allowe… (cont) http://deck.ly/~RwgWL
Yo, this high school reunion work is about to make me pull every last natural hair out of my head.
Thanx!! RT @TanikaRay: “@kimcoles: @TanikaRay hellloooooo! xoxooxoxx” Hi girl..love u as #natural hair icon..ur right where u belong.
@ms_d Thats natural after everything. You seemed incredibly shy at the time, less so in the morning.
@raphaelptw Hard to say. AV's natural supporters are pissed at the Lib Dems, so who knows which way they'll go.
A borra de café funciona como um inseticida natural e não faz mal para seres humanos, animais e plantas. #DengueMata #segov
Adele covers "Natural Woman" live! http://wp.me/pkpt1-8EO
RT @linaashar: Children are natural mimics: they act like their parents in spite of every attempt to teach them good manners.
Children are natural mimics: they act like their parents in spite of every attempt to teach them good manners. #parenting #education
@TheRickWilson @duchessrebecca Not natural.
All-natural, all-purpose Soy Lube! Use it everywhere! Cabin, car, cock! http://twitpic.com/4fur7f
The whole art of teaching is only the art of awakening the natural curiosity of young minds for the purpose of satisfying it afterwards.
@PaulaBertol me dijo legislador PRO q Gaby lucio nerviosa y q vos sos la sucesora natural #internaalrojovivoPRO
Wow, Wegmans in NY has a natural foods checkout lane with only natural 'impulse buy' items...very cool!
The natural force within each of us is that greatest healer of all. - Hippocrates
Natural History Museum's interactive film wins award | Natural History Museum http://bit.ly/eBbWvj
RT @iAmChuckie: #idontunderstandwhy females think they need to wear LOTS of make-up to be beautiful.. Natural Beauty beats everything.
I think Dede needs to get a half. Have him run at Jagielka. Also natural and passionate leader on field.
Thanks! RT @MaidenJane: RT @BigGirlJewelry: Keep synthetic sponges out of landfills #crochet these natural cut… (cont) http://deck.ly/~b0yel
RT @BigGirlJewelry: Keep synthetic sponges out of landfills #crochet these natural cuties instead! http://etsy.me/eA5gG2 #etsy
RT @deusprovidebit: this #clothdiaper is amazingly cute...right? http://etsy.me/fWjyBk #etsy #moms #baby #clothdiapers #natural #cute
!! RT @Teejjaayy: RT @MoshoodEdewor: Learn to let things take their natural course.What will be will be. #RealLifeShit
Simon Shrapel ACOSS president asks-'How do we galvanize same level of support for day2day issues as we do for natural disasters?' #acoss2011
Es publicidad engañosa, si realmente fuese "al natural" tendría que ser más peluda http://bit.ly/fVW1R5
The secret so that your kids can have natural good hair: marry an italian.
Muchas chicas creen que el que su pareja se comporte de forma sumisa y complaciente es natural y deseable. Yo digo a la chingada con eso.
@_AceEternal Meh. If a girl has hair on her... err nether regions I'm not put off. It's natural.
"In our reactionary world, it is a natural progression for us to say that the man had to go to work...... and that is why his energy is...
#OrganicChurch : a Christian community developed through making disciples in the natural social settings of a culture. http://ow.ly/4kPuv
@immyran hahahahaha wtf. but this one got natural beauty! she prettier in real life. ask zul! hahahahah
@AdamRutherford @profbriancox Here I thought natural history was safe—we already have Attenborough, after all; the cosmos just isn't enough?
@immyran @robotxphobia cos she scared you cannot control those malay natural instinct to procreate.
@sarrahsworld @etharkamal what I notice is disasters esp natural tend 2 make ppl "come out of the wood work" Kind of like a county fair.
New tweep: @darwinsdolls, tweeting on "the legacy of ecologists, botanists, entomologists and natural historians keeping up with the boys."
Tropism: the tendency to respond or move toward something by natural attraction
@libraryvoice Yep, the example is the natural symmetry that we see in life eg fractals, rainbows, etc.
SmartBird, la gaviota robot con vuelo (casi) natural y absolutamente autónomo, veo videos y me parece increíble.
Like a dust bowl depriving the midwest plains of a proper water source, Marquette's scoring drought is becoming a natural disaster.
La inteligencia artificial nunca podrá competir contra la estupidez natural.
RT @ThirdWorldGirl @BibiNetAlKole pshhh #naturalhairalltheway!!! But you look extra pretty, can't lie :-) < natural huurr fo life! &thanky
@JEESxorcismo @rosario_sasieta @funkyseiya la desnudez es lo más natural del mundo
@AhhhlexMoore well thats not exactly natural is it lol. and its still cheating!
There's so many natural disasters happening at a short amount of time, I think the world is changing slowly?
@AhhhlexMoore wit woo! more tanned than me lol altho...is this a natural tan? or a typical girly sunbed/spray/makeup/tinted moisturiser tan?
Photo Essay: New Zealand’s Natural Beauty http://bit.ly/eX44BM #travel via @seeke001 @photoasia
@sabhlok Read a load of material, We should use coal in the East and a mix of Natural gas and coal in the Western zone. No contest.
UK epidemiologist: an infant drinking 'unsafe' Tokyo water would get <1/3 of the I-131 he gets from natural background http://t.co/rA1la9k
Photo Essay: New Zealand’s Natural Beauty http://bit.ly/eX44BM #travel via @seeke001
The Natural Beauty of Our Planet - http://bit.ly/fAXlwk (PHOTOS) via @jmleclercq @photoasia @Bryant_Marden @cindyvriend @JumlaPhotoBlog
Posiblemente es solo mi amargosidad natural, posiblemente debería vivir en un lugar menos afectuoso.. como Antártida
@sabhlok Still not finding an on ground cost comparison in India that I can trust, we have coal too and natural gas, hydro good.
@dscofield @AmandaFenton Agreed. #BIF7 participants are natural connectors. @TheBIF team is on it. Stay tuned.
if a natural disaster is planning on hitting cali; please come when my dad is here. he's like a swedish macgyver, i'll survive no doubt
@AhhhlexMoore i do like him he seems nice, but theres that chloe! she makes katie price look natural, gemma! and now a drag queen!!!
Korey Maas, "Natural Law, Lutheranism, and the Public Good" Modern Reformation http://ow.ly/4k8ZJ
@graceupr Ademas de q "natural" es una falacia, el cianuro es natural.
Egyptian Magic is great for travelers; multi-use & all natural. RT @TravelingAnna: @jetsetfarryn Never heard of Egyptian Magic. Sounds good.
@IhateMS but it is liberal government like DPJ who is the cause. At this point It is human error. Not natural disaster any more.
@BigRedRanter Big Girls Blowse quote!!! "I'm gonna lose this weight the natural weight mum; Cigarettes & Ford pills"
@vadakkus Marriage is not a relationship of equals.Hubby is the dominant one,wife is the submissive one.That is the natural order.
@vadakkus Thts wat i said. That film ws an exception! Cant relate to the caste n all. And what his wife did was only natural @lillyvgp
Nate M: "The Lion Sleeps Tonight" (The Tokens) -- Nate is Andy's brother. Such sincerity and natural talent. And such nice dudes.
Si crees ese cuento q los remedios "naturales" son buenos y seguros: el cianuro es natural, las plantas lo usan como defensa.
Join The Revolution by Janet Callaway The Natural Networker http://t.co/vreqDw5 via @janetcallaway
@narcissus_echo [What's hard is simple? And what's natural comes hard?]
@a_spiraling no. Nap. My meds & natural internal clock have taken over. I've been sleeping all day & watching tv all night. I'm a night owl.
RT @arkarthick: The Natural Beauty of Our Planet: http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography via @jmleclercq @photoasia @cindyvriend @2morrowknight
VCU just put on a nightmarish spectacle that will haunt the dreams of the Purdue players for the rest of their natural born lives.
The Natural Beauty of Our Planet - http://bit.ly/fAXlwk | RT @jmleclercq @photoasia @cindyvriend @2morrowknight @arkarthick #EarthHour
The Natural Beauty of Our Planet - http://bit.ly/fAXlwk | #photography via @jmleclercq @photoasia @cindyvriend @2morrowknight
@xButtonNose l cut it like 2 years ago, trying to grow it natural without using relaxer and stuff.
RT @2morrowknight: The Natural Beauty of Our Planet - http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography /via @jmleclercq @photoasia @cindyvriend
"A alegria é o resultado natural da obediência do cristão à vontade revelada de Deus"
The Natural Beauty of Our Planet - http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography /via @jmleclercq @photoasia @cindyvriend
@deeleea lol you were a natural! Great to meet you x
Amazingly Shaped Natural Wonders of the World http://bit.ly/fkeTMf #photography via @brasonja
RT @43pixels: The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography (via @jmleclercq @photoasia @Bryant_Marden @cindyvriend)
@popups_cockups It's a tv program. They take in girls dressed in fake tan and very little clothes and gives them a new more natural style.
Es que ayer me dijeron fea =/ RT @jdn2015: Esooo!!! RT YeyaGe: Hoy me siento Bella, Libre y Natural ;)
RT @photoasia: Mixing Strobe Light with Natural Light on Location http://t.co/CiE2vGA #togs
RT @photoasia Mixing Strobe Light with Natural Light on Location http://bit.ly/eyH1Kc #togs
The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography via @jmleclercq @giselle2323 @photoasia RT @helios972 Wow! Stunning! ;D
The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography via @jmleclercq RT @giselle2323 @photoasia
rt @gpenman Beautiful! ~ RT @AnnTran_ The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk RT @jmleclercq @photoasia @giselle2323 #photos
Beautiful! ~ RT @AnnTran_ The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk RT @jmleclercq @photoasia @giselle2323 Stunning! #photos
RT @43pixels: The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography (via @jmleclercq @photoasia @Bryant_Marden @cindyvriend)
RT @AnnTran_: The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography || RT @jmleclercq @photoasia @giselle2323 Stunning!
The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography || RT @jmleclercq @photoasia @giselle2323 Stunning!
It's tough to be natural in front of the cameras when your childhood best friend keeps whispering "hey, you're on tv" just to throw you off.
Brad Littlejohn talks up Christian liberty & David VanDrunen's book Natural Law & the 2 Kingdoms http://ow.ly/4hB9w
The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk | #photography RT @photoasia @jmleclercq @affinity5 /via @arkarthick @Peepsqueak
The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk | #photography RT @photoasia @jmleclercq @affinity5 /via @arkarthick
The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk | #photography /via @arkarthick @photoasia @jmleclercq @affinity5
RT @arkarthick The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk | #photography RT @photoasia @jmleclercq @affinity5
The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk | #photography RT @photoasia @jmleclercq @affinity5
The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography via @jmleclercq @photoasia @brasonja
The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography RT @photoasia @jmleclercq @affinity5
The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography RT @photoasia @jmleclercq
Stunning! RT @photoasia: The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography via @jmleclercq
The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography via @jmleclercq RT @photoasia @brasonja
RT @debsylee: The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography via @jmleclercq RT @photoasia @brasonja <WOW>
Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photo via @jmleclercq @photoasia @brasonja @debsylee
The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography via @jmleclercq RT @photoasia @brasonja
The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography (via @jmleclercq @photoasia @Bryant_Marden @cindyvriend)
The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography via @jmleclercq RT @photoasia RT @Bryant_Marden
The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography via @jmleclercq RT @photoasia
The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography via @jmleclercq RT @photoasia
RT @photoasia: The Natural Beauty of Our Planet http://bit.ly/fAXlwk #photography via @jmleclercq
@pacotacomike Fighting the (20 year) age old phenomena that natural blondes come from elsewhere, Sweden.
El anterior? O.o RT @vikingoxx: @cerebral3 de pana te digo,te ves mejor con tu avatar natural,demasiado (cont) http://tl.gd/9b7aqa
@mhbx Re-establishing the Natural Order- http://bit.ly/g8DECN Nature seems so willing to be constrained by man… (cont) http://deck.ly/~WhOcT
@cerebral3 de pana te digo,te ves mejor con tu avatar natural,demasiado artificial el que pusistes,mis respetos.
@IhateMS 'あなた"が"良い一日を"過ごせるよう"に祈る！' is more natural:) We often say '素敵な(or 良い)1日になりますように！'
@prowag This is a collective action natural experiment just waiting to happen.
@Lucas_Wyrsch I think the same is true of any country, who must now rethink their nuclear plans in the face of any natural disasters
RT @mma_spain: Gas Natural Fenosa - Oficina virtual móvil http://bit.ly/hn2lNX /via @munoz_gallego // muy bien hecha esta app (-;
@lordwhatever @x7o I believe this is a colonial condition though. Irish education system arranged to stamp out natural curiosity and...
@etelberto Yo creo que muchos lo sabemos, ya que en México es lo mas natural que nuestro servicio de Internet falle.
Mi post. RT @jjimenez: Es otro, no Japón, el desastre natural actual que marcará nuestras vidas por @albertoartero: http://bit.ly/i2Vyg0
@kejames Midwest too! I work at a natural foods/vitamin shop. Ran outa all forms of iodine today.
Museum of Natural History - favorite architecture in NY! #nycgo @nycgo. Taken with #Instagram. http://twitpic.com/49scqp
@leejunlin you want maggi mee hair meh? haha.. i was going for the natural curls/waves look.
@tomwhitby My said startup was meant to create natural collaboration on learning. I WILL get back to it someday! #Edchat
Eight Spaces Left On Washington DC Trip (Mar 26): View the wooly mammoths in the Natural History museum or... http://tinyurl.com/4zsuvgd
Always amazed when people think they are... RT @kejames: Dear world, natural disasters are not punishment. For anything. Ever. Anywhere.
#sxsw @cloudcamp #devops: @wickett: @joshcorman reminds me to reiterate that DevOps and Rugged have very natural affinity.
RT @kejames: Dear world, natural disasters are not punishment. For anything. Ever. Anywhere. Even if they were, who are any of us to say so?
Two days left to apply for the Healthy Communities Coordinator or Project Officer positions! http://t.co/ZYf0SG9u #adelaide #jobs
All healthy and #vegan chili with a salad and a green juice: makes this sunny day even awesomer! [pic]: http://t.co/xfKC30kX
RT @CampbelltownSA: Vacancies: Healthy Communities Project Officer & Coordinator. http://t.co/4mRe7tfY #adelaide... http://t.co/m8EVV0qZ
Vacancies: Healthy Communities Project Officer & Coordinator. http://t.co/az01kiy2 #adelaide #jobs #health
@alex Yeah, I'd say it's healthy, as long as it's not packaged and gross.
We hit 2,000 Facebook fans over the holiday break! Thank you for your continued support. Happy and healthy 2012! http://t.co/AiOKINr7
Notwithstanding the somewhat inappropriate 'healthy' moniker, that's an impressive amount of nosh delivered for 12 quid.
Their £12 'Healthy Meal for 1' comes as: Lamb & brocolli curry, veg rice, 3 poppadoms, chapati, 4 bhajis, 4 samosas, full tray of salad+dips
Happy Holidays! We wish you a safe, healthy holiday season!
RT @campbelltownsa: Council, in partnership with Norwood P&StP, has secured a Healthy Communities Initiative Grant. http://t.co/4mkgsvon
"Bronies" make me seem like a normal, well-adjusted teenager with healthy interests.
LOL! RT @mynnkeng: @Xhezr - Kim Jong-Il died ah? Should get a person with the name of kim jong healthy to do the job ;)
Council, in partnership with Norwood Payneham & St Peters, has secured a Healthy Communities Initiative Grant. http://t.co/qEHGDJG7
what are the characteristics of a healthy relationship? #TNCoalition #saam
Dobbins: Generally, the media does not promote healthy environments and behaviors. #TNCoalition #saam
Prevention is a systematic process that promotes healthy environments & behaviors & reduces the likelihood/frequency of an incident,...
@sarahkatenorman Lovely! It's a healthy distance Kielder!
Ohh yep, it was thanks to @ErnestoRiley's mind RT @David_Boreanaz: Just had an insanely healthy energy shot! Time to rip it wide open!
@NauvalYzd @sadeethya Tweet ulang dong val. I kinda need a healthy dose of earth-bound love. Yg realistis gt. Ku tak suka yg ngawang2. :-)
RT @DuniaNexian: Tgl 10April di Car Free Day mampir ya ke dpn Runaway FO. Nexian Fun&Healthy W/ Prambors. Ada @buckskinbugle &byk hadiah
RT @pramborsbandung: Tgl 10April di Car Free Day mampir ya ke dpn Runaway FO. Nexian Fun&Healthy W/ Prambors. Ada @buckskinbugle &byk hadiah
Tgl 10April di Car Free Day mampir ya ke dpn Runaway FO. Nexian Fun&Healthy W/ Prambors. Ada @BuckskinBugle &bnyk hadiah ;) Cc: @DuniaNexian
"@pramborsbandung:Nexian Fun&Healthy W/ Prambors: CarFree Day, Jl. Dago (dpn Runaway FO). Bkl ad @BuckskinBugle KawulaMuda. Tgl 10April ini"
Nexian Fun&Healthy W/ Prambors: Car Free Day, Jl. Dago (dpn Runaway FO). Bkl ad @BuckskinBugle KawulaMuda. Tgl 10April ini. Cc: @DuniaNexian
Back from frenetic Sydney to the healthy Gold Coast, perfect morning for a ride (@ Gloria Jean's Coffees) http://4sq.com/ejnjUc
RT @DuniaNexian: "@pramborsbandung: Tgl 10April di Car Free Day mampir y k dpn Runaway FO. Nexian Fun&Healthy ... http://tmi.me/8xqCF
"@pramborsbandung: Tgl 10April di Car Free Day mampir y k dpn Runaway FO. Nexian Fun&Healthy W/ Prambors. Ad @BuckskinBugle &bnyk hadiah ;)"
@MyAgenda Good,everyone's healthy and happy. Only thing is, Mom's sad,it's the lil ones bday and she
Tgl 10April di Car Free Day mampir ya ke dpn Runaway FO. Nexian Fun&Healthy W/ Prambors. Ada @BuckskinBugle &bnyk hadiah ;) Cc: @DuniaNexian
RT @buckskin_bugle: Nexian Fun&Healthy w/ @pramborsbandung Ayo dtg KawulaMuda, tgl 10April di Car Free Day (dpn Runaway FO)
Nexian Fun&Healthy W/ Prambors: Car Free Day, Jl. Dago (dpn Runaway FO). Bkl ad @BuckskinBugle KawulaMuda. Tgl 10April ini. Cc: @DuniaNexian
PLAY GAME: Happy Pill: Place the happy pill to bounce un-healthy frowns upside down! http://dlvr.it/MbCBX g19-3-4a
PLAY GAME: Happy Pill: Place the happy pill to bounce un-healthy frowns upside down! http://dlvr.it/MZpQ2 g18-1-2a
PLAY GAME: Happy Pill: Place the happy pill to bounce un-healthy frowns upside down! http://dlvr.it/MZPkX g17-11-12a
PLAY GAME: Happy Pill: Place the happy pill to bounce un-healthy frowns upside down! http://dlvr.it/MYx7N g16-9-10p
PLAY GAME: Happy Pill: Place the happy pill to bounce un-healthy frowns upside down! http://dlvr.it/MYgyB g15-7-8p
#PLAY: Happy Pill: Place the happy pill to bounce un-healthy frowns upside down! http://dlvr.it/MXMX0 D #game FL
Happy Pill: Place the happy pill to bounce un-healthy frowns upside down! http://dlvr.it/MWwwk g12
PLAY THE GAME: Happy Pill: Place the happy pill to bounce un-healthy frowns upside down! http://dlvr.it/MWTL5 g11
PLAY THE GAME: Happy Pill: Place the happy pill to bounce un-healthy frowns upside down! http://dlvr.it/MVTmX g10
@TEDxMaastricht Thank you for perfect day of healthy thinking! Cheers
Oh-come-on! I hop online because I need to find some more healthy food ideas, only be greeted by this. #lifegroupfit http://t.co/DeZxCQq
@lilianyeung Yummy and healthy! *two thumbs up*RT @beatclassdotcom - Just wrapped a #Television #Pilot this morning .now going for a healthy run...#Filming is as fun as producing m...
Just wrapped a #Television #Pilot this morning .now going for a healthy run...#Filming is as fun as producing music the process is the same
RT @JaneBozarth: RT @SueSchnorr: Happy Birthday @hjarche - wishing you and happy and healthy year! #lrnchat
@TwRmcf a was gonna keep healthy & that tom.. went to 5s last night on my 2nd day of fitness.. BANG fucked the tendon on my big toe have to.
The Longevity Project:Surprising Discoveries for Health & Long Life from th... http://t.co/x79MKOE >> hard work = long healthy life
@dv3 that's fucking disgusting and not healthy at all
@CalleZorro A healthy sex life is good too!
@_tar0_ @demondogsports yah, give Zuko more cheese. not the healthy kind my humans tried to give me (i snubbed it) but fatty salty cheese!
@MatthewAGilmour Everything lol but it had to be healthy
Harry & David needs image upgrade http://ow.ly/4pHvP - @brucehorovitz my reco:ditch gift position-increase relevance 2 evryday healthy eatng
@hiqmaw gue suka havermouth + milo + susu + pisang :9 healthy breakfast with awesome flavor.
@cavsdan. A taste of things to come! How bout this team plus two or three lottery picks and cp3 Oh yeah, healthy Andy too! LET'S GO CAVS!
Having healthy kidneys is important because they help to remove waste products and excess fluid from the body. #NKM11
Drinking water is healthy, but does NOT mix well with crazy long work meetings. #lifegroupfit
Patient asked me an important question: why be healthy? My answer: because if just feels soooo good!
Aye gonna get really tough in the if Portland ever gets healthy.
@inkelectric ah you're fine, bread with fruit in is healthy. You ok? That message about your son made me chuckle
A healthy attitude is contagious but don't wait to catch it from others. Be a carrier. - Tom Stoppard
What do pecans & almonds have in common? They rank behind the king of #heart #healthy #nuts- Walnuts! From @CalorieLab http://bit.ly/eATqcI
you can ignore your healthy before you get sick . and after you get chronic disease all you can do is regret what you have done.
@Alexandria_R that's not healthy.
@louisfoo88 healthy!! gd!
Is lycopene still healthy, or was this all-ketchup diet for the past 4 years in vain? I'm scared. I will not read the most recent studies.
Eat for the body you want, not the body you have, eat healthy.
That is healthy/good for the soul, I think, #if you are being true and they are not still bothering you on the #inside :)..just never ever..
@JayElectronica I'm praying for your sister. I pray she will come through victorious and have a healthy baby. Keep us updated. Peace.
@HannahTysonn Not cool! Homework sucks. Hahahaha. But I can handle it! Yay! Lol. You have to sleep early :D Early sleep is healthy for ppl.
Got talked into buffalo wings...sometimes nothing else satisfies. Not exactly healthy but will chase them down with some celery. :)
India making cola from cow urine, it will be marketed as a 'healthy' alternative to Coke and Pepsi - http://ow.ly/4mKDz
@nateswart Sounds a lot like the healthy bacon-cracker-cheese items served at a home to remain anonymous...
Seeing healthy reefs is such a treat. Was quite something maneuvering around the taller acropora.
intensive chiong day tmr! Healthy living ftw @dansonang
#Spring is in the air! @DaculaPatch shares some great #cooking & #exercise tips to keep your heart healthy this Spring http://bit.ly/hKUS8V
@deeleea They are equally as healthy cos of all the vegies they sautee in delish sauce....!
Lakers just can't lose lol even without Kobe they're an automatic playoff team ... fully healthy they're the greatest team ever #realtalk
@SocialJulio Spring in Vegas? Rent a car & drive 1/2 hour to Red Rock for hiking. It's amazing and you can leave Vegas feeling healthy!
Parents can sneak healthy foods onto picky eaters' plates http://bit.ly/enxxVQ
#supercoach Out: J. Lyon, K. Gordon. In: M. Aubusson, B. Goodwin. (I'll bring Killer back when he's healthy, I guess)
@Biancanello Way too much to be healthy, would it be Family Guy by any chance, that Stewie is a true british gent
@cavsdan dasean butler has been cleared and is now healthy u need to check him out. He'll bring a spark #letsgocavs
every day, but sometimes? RT @itslenaxo 45. I would never smoke cigarettes everyday. Like some people at my school. I wanna live healthy!!
@beobal can I have the other half..? #snickers (bravo healthy dude!)
@annafdd What's and Eton mess.? Anyway, strawberries = fruit = healthy. Right? #dietwhatdiet
Dear Lisa, Stop thinking about it. It's not healthy at all. Love, Yourself
@DeirdreS a healthy #FF to you
@chrisrozwod that would suck. He finally becomes healthy and makes an all-star with another team. Fun fact Bowie traded for Buck Williams
@chrisrozwod sucks how history repeats itself. With Bowie/Jordan now Oden/Durant. You think Oden will ever be healthy? Healthy in pdx?
WSJ.com - Promoting Healthy Eating, on Terrence meck of #LGBT/nutrition/medical Palette Fund http://on.wsj.com/fLEHnh
@Chet6 @DishoomLondon i'm not the biggest bacon fan but it looks intriguing......i'm supposed to be eating healthy!
Happy #StPatricksDay! @Wane15 shares some healthy tips for your #heart this year: Green Veggies, not Green Beer! http://bit.ly/eoveLy #Irish
Let's hear from someone who lives a healthy digital life without being on Twitter #ucldh
@kian013: tmr is World Sleep Day! Let's sleep and be healthy yo!” if only people understood this
Online buyers rely on a healthy mix of search and social media throughout the purchasing process http://bit.ly/hMH269 via @emarketer
Staying healthy through sheer willpower. It seems to be working. #willnotgetsick #CANNOTGETSICK
I love my that my brain's response to my living healthy is never letting me sleep. Thanks, you bastard of a brain.
Photo: Lemongrass jumbo prawns, grilled asparagus, and lots of spinach. About as healthy as I can get at PF... http://tumblr.com/xrf1scj9gb
RT @ohranger: RT @NPCA: Free entry to national parks April 16-24 for Nat'l Park Week! Healthy Parks, Healthy People: http://1.usa.gov/han4kD
@RachelMacik sometimes you just gotta vent some steam with a healthy dose of sarcasm LOL! Thx for the RT!
@eolistpetite But yes - there was a healthy amount of chedder atop my crumpets - yum!
#sxsw @cloudcamp #devops: @wickett: "The tough questions: Am I healthy? Am I secure?" Infosec is called "jaded, paranoid".
Healthy Eating Awards scheme has been launched today in #Middlesbrough!... http://fb.me/G2gOioJH
OH: "all I've eaten is BBQ - that can't be healthy?" "Yeah, well, have you seen any old people in Austin?" "point taken - I'll have salad"
@RacheeRoo It's definitely not healthy - all brains need a rest now and again :-)
I've come to the conclusion I think too much. Far too much. It's not healthy.
@ese_mismo_ Amazing superb I need to stay mentally healthy - any ideas? http://leco.gl/1Baw Trustworthy
Not healthy TV programming this evening. Only shootings and wars. Bah...watching sporadicly
I said homemade food not fast food RT: @leelo124 Mango1027 root bear ,pop tarts and cherry turnovers i thought you liked to eat healthy ?
RT @xolotl wow #Blackboard CEO @michaelchasen's 2009 compensation is was $8.4M-thats a healthy chunk of the entire #Sakai community budget
@Heyrainbows both excited and frighten..kinda bittersweet :) yeah I mean..9 months doing nothing, my god that can't b healthy right? haha
@FunyGrl she has a cough :/ are you guys nice and healthy yet?
Had breakfast at Pret A Manger. Variety of healthy sandwiches. Didn’t know which one to get. Killa pesto, avocado, balsamic chicken, etc.
@MissAppiah @xButtonNose oh really? Hmmm and you both have healthy hair. Mmmmm niceee.
If you are at #Nutracon, be sure to attend the Healthy Aging Ingredient Idol competition at 2pm today and vote for pTeroPure Pterostilbene!
@RacheeRoo I like healthy food...
@Terry_Hodge_92 unlike some people I actually like healthy stuff!!.. Plus the flapjacks covered in chocolate, they're good too...
@Terry_Hodge_92 it's not real rabbit food... It's just healthy stuff
And I want a healthy man.. "@frhn: Staring at breasts increases heart health - http://bit.ly/et4HVY"
@StorySoid "FB is a Trap" We're back to that processed sugar (Junk Food) vs. brown rice (healthy fodder) discussion? Addiction?
Maybe “not normal” in a healthy way, but still not normal.
@PoloWill right. because that would defeat the purpose of eating healthy. lol
@RebelSanders *facepalm* Yeahhhhh... that's a healthy way to live. Why do you need to stay awake so badly?
Avoid becoming a statistic, #women! Great story in @FreeP detailing what #girls need to do to encourage healthy #hearts http://bit.ly/ebqYxo
@_jonb Very interesting I need to stay mentally healthy - any ideas? http://leco.gl/1vhm Glorious
@suvama doesn't tourtiere have most of the food groups already in it..sounds healthy ;)
@LivefromNoVA congrats & glad to hear mom & baby are healthy!
@deniseleeyohn LOTS of cool concepts on the show! Especially interested to see how the healthy concepts do, since that's the big trend.
RT @freerangekids: SO interestng:Wal-Mart demands prods go green/healthy http://bit.ly/f2g5IS |"bigger stick than any fines govt can impose"
@KiidKeo yea she's young tho. Healthy choices and sports would help
LOL RT @BiIIWaIton When healthy, Andrew Bynum’s nose for the ball brings to mind a rambunctious foxhound descending mightily upon his prey.
Bill is smoking a fatty today, folks! RT @BiIIWaIton When healthy, Andrew Bynum’s nose for the ball brings t… (cont) http://deck.ly/~KE7RM
wow RT @BiIIWaIton: When healthy, Andrew Bynum’s nose for the ball brings to mind a rambunctious foxhound descending mightily upon his prey.
When healthy, Andrew Bynum’s nose for the ball brings to mind a rambunctious foxhound descending mightily upon his prey.
Addicting -- http://twitpic.com/46mf6s -- and healthy...well, kind of! Yummy (",)
courtesy of @luisjavierdiaz “@TheSunQueen: Great Q: what is #netDE doing to promote healthy lifestyle? It's cheaper for the state. #OurRev”
@Cherryvodka88 But healthy!!!
@BiIIWaIton Bill, great to see you. Met you once as a kid. I recently explained why I'd take a healthy you as the C on my all time team.
OH: Your ulcer has a healthy heartbeat.
"Information Stories Tell of Personal Stakes in Healthy Info Communities" http://wp.me/p1mjr5-d1
Happy #FollowFriday! @SocialChatsSF @LabTestsOnline @LisaCollierCool @_AACC @BrophyMarcUSAT @DiabeticLiving Have a #heart #healthy weekend!
@joelwsmith congratulations. saw pictures on facebook...he's adorable! happy to hear everyone is healthy. and LOVE the name!
@val04 I would've gone w/ big-boned - but healthy! - Etta in supporting different female body types w/ Diana acknowledging as much.
@alexiabautista yeppers. healthy my ass! ha ha. and thank you.
@ArtChicinTX @beckymochaface I am sensing a very healthy Tweetup....
@hauntedserenity ... soy and wheat and fiber and nothing else, but that is not too healthy, you need protein and calcium and such.
Healthy groceries are so pretty! Nary an Oreo or ketchup chips in sight. Or a baguette sadly. http://yfrog.com/h0pr5qjj
Yay, #SteveJobs is presenting and he looks healthy(ish)
@John__Mee glad to here u eat eat healthy not many like to do that. just as good i think, :)
I'm at Kensington Fitness Center (202 Caton Ave, at E 2nd St, Brooklyn) http://t.co/nEWMmSAo
Sudden change of schedule ... (at Fitness First Platinum) — http://t.co/kpXFwhtm
Good Groupon deal: Ten Individual Day Passes Including Access To Gym, Pool and Classes for £19 at LA fitness (87% Off) http://t.co/qx6VGhTO
A Digital Revolution in Health and Fitness Is Coming: How to Ride the Wave http://ow.ly/4vDHv -a piece i wrote for consumer electronics blog
@RugbyByDilbert cool! I need to work on my fitness also , i dont mind some passing
#Soytanrudo que I totally hung up on the LA Fitness chick this a.m. because I was getting my sleep on & she interrupted. #losiento
@RugbyByDilbert and fitness helps you maintain your technique in a game. Important for reducing risk of injury (this was my main motivator)
@RugbyByDilbert but passing/kicking/fitness is ok for me.
Top 10: Die besten iPhone-Apps für Sportler. http://bit.ly/eYin6R #ski #fitness #biking /via @gesundheitswirt
@TwRmcf a was gonna keep healthy & that tom.. went to 5s last night on my 2nd day of fitness.. BANG fucked the tendon on my big toe have to.
I just became the mayor of Klein Fitness on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/dGoGRg
At Fitness First The Curve. I love this gym. It's good to be back. Can't wait to get on my FIT + gym routine again. :)
I'm at MPower Total Fitness in Whitefish Bay, WI http://gowal.la/c/3SVod
Planet Fitness opens first Greenville club http://bit.ly/hYp7XK
@nateswart We have also found Just Dance Kids and Just Dance 2 to be great fun and fitness
@SLRenson oh yeah! We have Wii fit in now, but may switch to Wii Sports shortly. Never tried EA Fitness - any good?
@nateswart I'd say you can get EA Fitness or WII Fit and go to town, right??
Trying to figure out the best way to accomplish both #morningfaith and now #lifegroupfit - fitness stuff may be a lunch time focus for me.
@NauvalYzd @agusitem tapi kl udh jadi bos kan udh rapi lagi secara udh mampu bayar fitness :)) *lama ya nunggunya*
I'm at MPower Total Fitness in Whitefish Bay, WI http://gowal.la/c/3QFAy
@Tharwacolamus Amazon now markets yoga and fitness gear http://best-yoga-clothes.info/Amazon/media/dance-meditation-of-om-by-arzell-nelson
The 'Fitness Function' of Economic and Political Systems [#Video] http://goo.gl/fb/f7rLl #erf2011 #complexity
Interesting - I walk a mile every day, just "commuting" to work. If I walk home for lunch, it's 2 miles. #fitness
this is gonna hurt.. @ MPower Total Fitness http://gowal.la/c/3PSjq
i pretty much have no food in my house.. this will make for a very difficult first fitness bootcamp this evening... #crap
@AhhhlexMoore oh deary, that wasn't meant to sound dirty, but ahwell! Listening to the fitness beats tomorrow!! :)
I'm at Anytime Fitness http://4sq.com/f5EGAe
Hausmann and the ‘fitness function’ of economic and political systems http://goo.gl/fb/yfXlL #erf2011 #democracy
@InAStateOfFlux Alarming number of just-back-to-fitness, not-back-to-form players too.
Gold’s Gym Rolls Out Express Clubs http://ow.ly/4igNQ via @clubindustry | what will be diff/better vs. planet or snap fitness?
@RenJie86 I want fitness not fatness! Lol:
@greythorne oops think it was start fitness
#erf2011 Ricardo Hausmann: can politics be the fitness function?
#erf2011 Ricardo Hausmann: what's the fitness function of public inputs?
#erf2011 Ricardo Hausmann: complex system have the capacity to self organise with fitness function that creates feedback loop - #evolution
Wonneröllchenrichtig. :)) RT @TillaPe: @Heartcore Hö? Fitness-Studio?
Does that mean all creationists are fitness nuts? RT @sweatscience: How evolution keeps you on the couch http://t.co/1DeHxuQ
Total Soccer Fitness: Total Soccer FitnessComplete guide to soccer conditioning. Untapped market. Very high conv... http://bit.ly/gYdn6w
should exercise. i fell of the fitness wagon at first time of p90x, but should persevere at least do some breakdance sweat like bodyrock.tv.
@alvinng Fitness – if it came in a bottle, everybody would have a great body. http://ow.ly/31VUN?=ndy0
Fitness kak RT @had_ryan: @nabylsungkar mau kemana enaknya...
I start a fitness boot camp tomorrow morning at 5:30am for the next 4 weeks. Why did I think this was a good idea??
@Val04 Better step up your game, bro: Army's new fitness tests add taste of battlefield - http://yhoo.it/gK7sih
Never had an ex try try so hard to win me back until LA Fitness. But you haven't changed. A fat ponytailed hippie still teaches spin, no?
@mikaylacarson Oooooh! Keep me updated on your fitness goals!! I love talking with people about it, and challenging each other!
March fitness stuff: down 15lbs. No refined sugar, little gluten. 30mins-1hr of exercise daily. 3 day 'fruit cleanse'. 2.5L of water daily.
@deniseleeyohn enjoy your content. I am looking for a quality brand valuation firm for a global fitness player. Any suggestions ?
The Flirty Girl Fitness Pole costs but one dollar. There has to be some irony there.
@alvinng Ya, fitness/stamina gotta slowly build up...
@alvinng Well start slow & build up your fitness level...
I checked in at Bally Total Fitness (2920 Aborn Square Rd) on #Yelp http://bit.ly/axV0GX
I checked in at Bally Total Fitness (2920 Aborn Square Rd) on #Yelp http://bit.ly/axV0GX
@kpantiii lmfao it's pretty easy it's like a fitness test and lol ;) you kno I would
I checked in at Bally Total Fitness (2920 Aborn Square Rd) on #Yelp http://bit.ly/axV0GX
I'm now the Duke of Bally Total Fitness on #Yelp! http://bit.ly/ibqoPf
I checked in at Bally Total Fitness (2920 Aborn Square Rd) on #Yelp http://bit.ly/axV0GX
@ Laco. Fitness, kickboxen.
RT @pinoyfitness 143 GO - Run the Miles, Share the Love - February 27, 2011 | Pinoy Fitness http://tinyurl.com/65uvemo
I checked in at Bally Total Fitness (2920 Aborn Square Rd) on #Yelp http://bit.ly/axV0GX
There are those who will express doubt, disbelief or some other negative reaction to your fitness goals & progress. Prove them wrong!!
Ponte en forma con GAIN Fitness: http://t.co/7gWnNm1 vía @alt1040 | Creo que va a ser un buen amigo cuando retome mis entrenamientos...
BodMoxie is about feeling beautiful and making your body better through fitness and health.
I've forgotten how much cycling makes me wanna fall off the bike in a dead faint! ANYWAY, mas maganda group classes sa fitness kesa gold's.
@andybaldwin "U.S. Navy Doctor, Deep Sea Diver, Health/Fitness advocate, Ironman Triathlete, Marathon Runner..."Welcome Dr.Baldwin San Diego
@LadyLoveliness I feel a fitness DVD coming on... #watchthisspace x
@LadyLoveliness That is exactly my fitness routine. Minus the skating... x
Need a little fitness kick-start? The Rec Center's "Walk Your Way to Fitness" spring incentive program starts Monday http://bit.ly/eFVFtl
@wscruggs lol 6:30 usually. Gotta get my fitness on!
looking forward to try out Holmes Place Börseplatz tonight with @heckmueller #Gym #Fitness
has been sent Kinect - Your Shape: Fitness Evolved: http://LOVEFiLM.com/r/QQiJ0Xw
RT @deniseleeyohn: Latest brand as business brief features rpts on future of mktg, retail, health, & fitness |subscribe: http://ow.ly/3T76r
just released latest brand as business brief featuring reports on future of mktg, retail, health, & fitness | subscribe: http://ow.ly/3T76r
Tomorrow is a new day. Focus and commit to your diet and fitness regimen, starting with breakfast (or pre-breakfast workout). Go for it!
@mattdfletch @wholesomepig meaning. I am paying $300 a week for a top fitness professional who has trained with the best in the world...
Going on your honeymoon? Make fitness part of your trip! Here's some ideas for locations and activities ~ http://tinyurl.com/4arlfk7
Got to love those late night workouts. (@ Xsport Fitness) http://4sq.com/dRf1gb
Jack Lalanne, father of fitness, honored during a memorial celebrating his life ~ http://tinyurl.com/4exas6a
Happy Groundhog Day! (@ First In Fitness) http://4sq.com/gPWYLg
@CHADinAMSTERDAM but the most popular sport to practice is fitness/cardio both with men and with women.
@amandaang7 ya cause I was talking to this guy today! he sign on fitness first which is damn ex, and only need to pay about 600 a year!
@BCRE8TV Thanks for following, here's my invites Health & Fitness: http://tinyurl.com/6hazyee Make Money FREE!: http://tinyurl.com/6yfrg4r
Achievement unlocked!: Lose 1 stone! +1 fitness!
#Toronto #fitness instructors who need work: RT @JUDYSGROUP: HELP WANTED!...LOOKING FOR INSTRUCTORS...contact info@judysgroupfitness.ca
I just ousted @mikeyork1 as the mayor of Bounce - The fitness zone on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/91bRfQ
What sorts of fitness gadgets (and / or websites) do you use to track your workouts? http://gdg.to/g2KT3M
I'm at First In Fitness (1 Blanchard Ct, Montpelier) http://4sq.com/fTGwFC
@jongzilla is that the ladies health and fitness show that is going to air?
RT @PrecedentMag: Law grad finally passes NH Bar on 8th try, but denied license on character and fitness grounds. Ouch http://bit.ly/hnKO6U
Hey locals! Do you enjoy being ripped off by an unapologetic staff? Rush on over to Thriv Fitness Center and join up! #caveatemptor
Personally I find couples who work out together quite annoying. (@ Thriv Fitness Center) http://4sq.com/gAJuMs
Law grad finally passes NH Bar on 8th try, but denied license on character and fitness grounds. Ouch http://bit.ly/hnKO6U (via @lawyernexus)
Just saw this on Amazon: 'Zumba Fitness' by Majesco Sales Inc. (Nov 18,... for $39.99 http://amzn.to/ggVrLg
I'm at Xsport Fitness (960 W Dundee Rd, Arlington Heights) http://4sq.com/e0YoDF
Learn how to start a ‘Spiritual Fitness Club' and maybe survive the experience. #kindle #novel http://t.co/Pc58qZl [iPhone download link!]
LIVE! Saddleback's Daniel Plan health webcast -Drs Mark Hyman & Daniel Amen & Fitness Pro. Join 8,200 signed up! www.danielplan.com
I need something to motivate my fitness regime tomorrow..
RT @greencelebrity: Celebrity Death: #Health and #fitness giant Jack LaLanne dead at 96? http://t.co/ReF63dD
Interesting biz model turn. RT @ariegoldshlager: [Pay as you don't go] The Gym-Pact Fitness Plan: http://bit.ly/eavuwJ Via: @deniseleeyohn
@python2010 -Lots of FREE stuff in Work @Home,Make Money Online,Self Improvement,Education,Health,Fitness & more: www.empoweronline.us
[Pay as you don't go] The Gym-Pact Fitness Plan: http://bit.ly/eavuwJ Via: @deniseleeyohn
Harvard grads turn gym business model on its head; fitness plan members pay more if they don’t work out http://ow.ly/3JvUC | love it!
"If I put inferior food in my body today, I'm going to be inferior tomorrow." - Fitness guru Jack LaLanne, RIP http://bit.ly/fEgTrR
@missferran Jack LaLanne, Yes! That's whom I thought of when you mentioned the fitness aspect.
motivasi fitness hari senin pagi: jam 10 pagi ada yang kelas pilates soalnya hahaha
@abc7 so-called father of fitness?
Jack LaLanne, Father of Fitness Movement, Dies at 96 - http://nyti.ms/fM1aiH
In the meantime, BodMoxie will keep up to date on the latest fitness news.
Working on the launch of the BodMoxie website in the next few weeks! The site will focus on fitness for women. More info to come soon.
you could have sworn he'd live forever. RT @latimes: Jack LaLanne, fitness guru, dies at 96 http://lat.ms/hbkW8t
On the weekends do you do a workout or do you do an activity for fitness?
@YogaChicky Sure, I'd love to help make your ideas happen. I used to be active; the "female fitness" focus turns me away. Not this week.
@TheChickAbides We're Glad to follow you. Follow us back for Health Fitness updates.
@praveenravi @dpavanm @Drag9n sakuu.. I cant read any more fitness stuff.. Because i dont do any of those..
I'm at Xsport Fitness (960 W Dundee Rd, Arlington Heights) http://4sq.com/fQ0xbe
I'm at 24 Hour Fitness (1375 Campbell, Plano Rd., Richardson) http://4sq.com/eEKfiI
Heart beats 100k times/day http://bit.ly/43j1JA RT @chriskresser How 2 become diabetic in 5 easy steps http://bit.ly/gWcozI #health #fitness
I finally started using @Runkeeper. (Good job, team!) Superb example of mobile app for fitness.
So my new fitness blog...I wanted to call it FitterIreland but since I'm moving back to London...any ideas? (@Leoie)
@m_dot Following you on Twitter,Follow us back for Health and Fitness updates.
Had a great workout yesterday and today. Fitness makes you feel so good!
Great blog post from @deniseleeyohn on tech innovation in health & fitness. "It's bout the user not the technology." #fitness
Learn more about #exercise from our Fargo store's #fitness expert Josh Nogowski: http://bit.ly/dPm56N
RT @deniseleeyohn on innovation in health & fitness & beyond http://ow.ly/3D8Ms applies to yogatailor
I'm at 24 Hour Fitness http://4sq.com/eni3R7
I'm at 24 Hour Fitness (1375 E. Campbell Rd., Richardson) http://4sq.com/hkBG6m
"on tech innovation in health & fitness and beyond" http://ow.ly/3D8Ms new brand as biz bite post on innovating with impact
I'm at 24 Hour Fitness http://4sq.com/g4SsBz
I'm at Anytime Fitness (14 Kings Cross R, Diamant Hotel, Mezzanine Level,, Potts Point) http://4sq.com/eGrHR7
I just became the mayor of Anytime Fitness on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/bND1ok
Okay who is this 'James' who gave my number to the fitness first peeps? I'm coming for you Danny!!!
I'm at Xsport Fitness (960 W Dundee Rd, Arlington Heights) http://4sq.com/g87ClT
@LaNotteStellata I go to planet fitness! $10/mo open 24/7 all new equipment and tv's. Why do people pay so much for gym memberships?
Workin up a sweat!! (@ 24 Hour Fitness) [pic]: http://4sq.com/eNYskX
Would you believe that quote was from Plato? Check out our fitness gear to get yourself in the mood! http://bit.ly/gddrzl
Parks and Rec programs now online! Browse Family Programs, Trips, Fitness, Cooking, Sports and more at http://tinyurl.com/32k5ujg #roa #rke
Register for Spring Parks and Rec programs online! Browse Trips, Fitness, Cooking, Sports and more at http://tinyurl.com/32k5ujg #roa #rke
@gamalian selamat ngakak d pekanbaru RT @erlanggamohamad: @syamharyo dab, sesuk aku bar ujian kancani fitness yo? tenanan lho iki.. hehehe..
Wuuuushh... Ngerii daah skr.. :p RT @erlanggamohamad: @syamharyo dab, sesuk aku bar ujian kancani fitness yo? tenanan lho iki.. hehehe..
@syamharyo dab, sesuk aku bar ujian kancani fitness yo? tenanan lho iki.. hehehe..
109m² com qualidade e ótima localização! 3 dorm, 2 vagas, terraço gourmet, fitness e muito mais para vc ter mais tempo no seu dia!
@idearella Fitness lover? This ebook provide probably the most effective procedures for health lover,http://bit.ly/cylAEB?=mtm4
@Fitarella Even cooler, I have some fitness goals. It's like you were made for me. Can't wait to fully check out your site.
@python2010 -Lots of FREE stuff in Work @Home,Make Money Online,Self Improvement,Education,Health,Fitness & more: www.empoweronline.us
@jjash Any resolutions? I just got Runkeeper Pro from iTunes - Free until end of January maybe I should make resolution around fitness
Fitness people who have iPhones, RunKeeper Pro is free until January FYI http://ow.ly/3wfot
@missmalin I need that for health reasons,hndi for figure enhancement.haha! :) try mo sa nestle fitness kng merong ganun.kc ung cd ko dun eh
@jing_ting he will blame the weather for not giving his team match fitness.
I recommend using the dividers to separate lists, notes from meetings, tracking of fitness stuff, etc. #StaplesBrandProducts
Arc has dividers that snap in & out just like the pages. Create sections for tasks, errands, fitness, etc. #StaplesBrandProducts
I'm almost mayor on @foursquare at the local 24 Hour Fitness. Well, it's because I check-in as I drive by it.
@ekgarcia BEST: Buy a whole chicken and bake or grill it. Serve vegetables, too.
@Louis_Plumb We've a number of root vegetables and mushrooms, and a selection of breads from Mr Coppercrow ...
So its better to eat vegetables than fruits....of course the nasty shit is better -__-
I think it's sad that they keep pork stuff by the vegetables at easy way. For, you know, flavor.
If candy is so bad for you, why does it taste like candy? You're move vegetables.
@tomtorre Nope! :) I got popcorn, but thats it for the unhealthy food! I bought vegetables, salad, and a nice stirfry sauce for the veg :)
HealthPartners' Averbeck: next working on increasing fruits/vegetables, physical activity #IHI
Photo: Straight outta the Paleo Cookbook: beef stew with vegetables! April also made a side of roasted... http://tumblr.com/xrf1u3k2hp
RT @ChefBoiMajor_: I don't wanna marry, I just wanna have sex with you, then throw you to the side like a fat kid do vegetables - @PoloWill
I don't wanna marry, I just wanna have sex with you, then throw you to the side like a fat kid do vegetables - @PoloWill
@girlgatsby You will absolutely need a bigger dress then. How about some vegetables instead?
@CatholicDrinkie shaving, fasting, vegetables, no twitter, water for Lent.
Productive Produce — Bang for your buck in the produce section - http://ow.ly/49GeQ #fruits #vegetables #nutrition
I'm cooking 7 different vegetables tonight. Guess how many my kids will eat?? :/
Stop complaining! Get over it...give it your best shot, might as well...we'll end up turning like vegetables and die sooner or later anyway!
@_maryashley Sushi was good/overpriced, the rice/vegetables was just okay. Good for a one time thing. $4.50 for an avocado roll? Sheesh.
I'm not sure what "rapporteur" means, but apparently it involves root vegetables and astroglide. UN jackasses crack me up. #cambodia #UN
@greythorne @gobi_one Never knew that vegetables had fingers
Has anyone made a calendar (eg .ics) of seasonal vegetables (in UK)?
@pugwash1962 its just a can of vegetables... but yeah they are messy i guess
@pugwash1962 one 1/4 cup serving of Manwich contains or is the equivalent of 1/2 cup of vegetables. if that helps?
@MikeGruz 'Ooo, I only eat vegetables that haven't been harmed!'
@ProfBruce not to mention the higher consumption of fast food, and lower consumption of fruits and vegetables.
@AndreaShredder What? It doesn't chop vegetables?
@Kenerics my intention was to go for another exercise class but now I'm not so sure. I will juice up some vegetables and see how I feel
@NOLLYWOODSCENE I've only been juicing vegetables so far so in ya face!
DocuTicker: How Much Do Fruits and Vegetables Cost? http://bit.ly/gcdrmM
French fries are considered vegetables in the states??? My gosh??? @eunicetanyl
Singapore: farm skywards RT @SherryPCMO @ComfyPaws @frugalgrower: Vertical farm produces 5 times more vegetables http://bit.ly/hy7DOA #photo
@Greg_Dillon Thanks! Low carbs diet. No sugar, no fructose. Basically salads, meats, cheeses and a few vegetables.
#FF I'd like to be in Bermuda with these three but I wouldn't eat @poptopvw ’s vegetables @janebbrown @mikebeak
Suggested Vegetables for Indoor Gardening | Urban Organic Gardener - http://ow.ly/3FpFv
RT @robinbloor: I didn't fight my way to the top of the food chain to eat vegetables.
@CrankyClown @xoonline haha! So turkeys are chickens and chickens are vegetables! #ArgumentForVegetarianism
@dorritos @XOonline I've raised chickens. They are basically walking vegetables. I have no problem eating them. :-)
But as a follow-up to the last RT, I give The Big List of Vegetables! http://bit.ly/cgflpW @hinthr @crossingculture
Have successfully completed my #newyearresolution. It was "eat more vegetables". Had some yesterday, had more today. Job done.
New Years Resolution #1 - Eat more seasonable fruit and vegetables http://fb.me/zget6NZC
@JacksonB that's true, but it's a failure that I am utterly addicted to! Dissolving vegetables hmmmmmmmm ^_^
Overheard: "Vegetables not good for you. Vegetables does give you gas." #Trinidad
Ditto! RT @peggyflanagan Wow, vegetables have never tasted so good. #thingsimissedduringchristmas
Can you get your child to effortlessly consume 14 organic fruits and vegetables? http://tinyurl.com/2bh2vgs
Can you get your child to effortlessly consume 14 organic fruits and vegetables? http://tinyurl.com/2bh2vgs
Can you get your child to effortlessly consume 14 organic fruits and vegetables? http://tinyurl.com/2bh2vgs
Can you get your child to effortlessly consume 14 organic fruits and vegetables? http://tinyurl.com/2bh2vgs
Eat less meat. Prevent blockage 4 #healthy #heart http://bit.ly/43j1JA RT @eDiets Holidays: great time to enjoy colorful fruits & vegetables
Can you get your child to effortlessly consume 14 organic fruits and vegetables? http://tinyurl.com/2bh2vgs
Create your own platters with a selection of original sott'oli vegetables http://fb.me/MQrcrDNq
Can you get your child to effortlessly consume 14 organic fruits and vegetables? http://tinyurl.com/2bh2vgs
Can you get your child to effortlessly consume 14 organic fruits and vegetables? http://tinyurl.com/2bh2vgs
@Annieinaustin Other ingredients: green beans, fresh pickled ginger, omelette slices, seasoned rice and tasty, mysterious Asian vegetables!
how do you #fertilize your #vegetables, edible plants, #organic plants? www.urbanfarmsorganic.com/survey.html
slow roasted pork belly. "The vegetables are there only for show. There’s no point pretending that this is a healthy dish"
@jplaub For several hours now! Trying to uninstall but it's refusing to budge >:| I'm so Steam'd, I'm like a whole… meal of… vegetables.
I am the effing rumplestilskin of frozen vegetables.
@LunaSelene @bipolarbearx I just like vegetables...give me a wrap loaded with spinach, sprouts, tomatoes, cukes and hummus. NOM.
Quote of the night "he's the kind of guy who grows his own vegetables"
WHOLESOME VEGETABLES! MEN! EAT YOUR VEGETABLES!!!
"When we see....the BOUNTY of fruits and vegetables....we are...VERY excited."
@HollyHadsell no, not really. a lot of them have already started (i.e. cooking with hay, fried vegetables, etc).
@Zendaya96 I'm a huge fan! I love you so much! What's ur favorite fruit?
@SumPutz -"Get some corn liquor in a fruit jar. . . .straight from your favorite still" Headin' Way Down South for some smooth Blues!!
whats your favorite fruit?: — Banana! http://4ms.me/dUWONo
favorite quote today "SHE SELLS WOLF TICKETS ALL DAY BUT CAN'T BUST A GRAPE IN A FRUIT FIGHT"
How can my favorite fruit do this to me? How? Tell me how?!Why me, oh why me?! #Kdrama
Q: What's your favorite fruit? A: Watermelon: http://yearbook.com/ask-me-anything/s60gy
REALLY?? I Had NO Idea! :) @Cheek_: MINE TOO!!! RT @eL_QuEzzyO: Favorite Fruit: Pineapple
A favorite at #GFWE the just released #Merlot 2008 from #AngelsGate. WOW! Great fruit. http://yfrog.com/47embsj
(@MonsterSmiles) Favorite fruit? / Fruta favorita? — apples http://4ms.me/dpl9fm
RT @PaulyPeligroso: Fruit Punch is my favorite drink/hate crime.
RT @PaulyPeligroso: Fruit Punch is my favorite drink/hate crime.
Currently eating pineapples.... my favorite fruit.
RT @DopeBeIiebers: #bieberfact Justin's favorite type of gum is Juicy Fruit. RETWEET if u have tried that before (:
(@MonsterSmiles) Favorite fruit? / Fruta favorita? — The Tangerine :) http://4ms.me/dsegHv
@sherylnome1101 favorite fruit - 7 Powerful Health Benefits of Pomegranate http://btly.brb.dj/8g86k { radashka c another pom fan. Lol♐}
@MamtaTandel Jalebi is my favorite fruit. (ok. ok, just kidding!) It is my favorite sweet though.
Thinking of something to eat for lunch? Partner it with your favorite Fruit Magic drink. Have one delivered now!... http://fb.me/GLhAJNoD
Bananas are my favorite fruit (:
Theetje zetten, liptontea forest fruit my favorite!
my favorite fruit crisp dish-blogged- http://alisaburke.blogspot.com/2010/11/cranberry-carmel-apple-crisp.html
Q: What are your 3 most favorite and 3 least...A: 3 fav pizza steak fruit non fav fish be...: http://yearbook.com/ask/beach_babe12/rl9vv
Top Five Favorite Fruit Candle Scents - http://bit.ly/aFrDFZ
parentsmagazine Parents Magazine RT @parentsmagazine Complete this sentence! Our favorite easy after-school snack is... FRESH FRUIT :)
@FollowSavvy scooby doo fruit snack are my favorite. scooby is the best flavor :)
2 plates of patoles and idk how many plates imma eat of fruit salad <3 my mommy made my favorite food today :)
Dinosaur fruit snacks from @Meijer are my favorite!
It’s time to pick my favorite #fruit. Apples. You were expecting something else?
Ratatouille Crepes,Tropical Fruit Scramble,Frittata, Chai Tea French Toast r all done Sunday! Hurry in so you don't miss your favorite!
greentweet: Good morning! Remember Fruit and Veggie Friday? Play along with #FVF and share your favorite recipes! To... http://bit.ly/ad90lo
what's your favorite fruit? — Apple http://4ms.me/a8DN1H
RT @nicksilly: I paid less for my 12-pack of cokes than my half-gallon of milk yesterday. ~~ Stop buying organic. You need the hormones.
Scholastic #CIO SaadAyub - revenue growth thru organic growth or acq or by saving costs http://bit.ly/dT8lSH
@nateswart Just gotta be sure the fruit is organic.
@shakasisulu @amuzweni shakaaaaaa<<<boom>>>collaborative thinkin, organic flow thrus...i've died n gone 2 large social transformation heaven
RT @keithgiles: Join me on Organic Church Today: http://www.organicchurchtoday.com/profile/KeithGiles #organicchurch
Im gonna miss this guy!!! RT @BronxZoosCobra Does anyone know if the Whole Foods in Columbus Circle sells organic mice?
Just restarted River Ford veggie box & for the 1st time, got a Meat Box too. Awesome value - all organic, freerange & locally sourced
I'm seriously overhauling what goes in my body. Through my mouth. In a FOOD sense. Ahem. Veg-ISH, organic, less. My kingdom for a juicer.
@redhairband organic wool, I hope?
Add Chicken for an even dozen! RT @SlashSimon: 11 things that are better when organic. http://t.co/QYsrMyy
11 things that are better when organic. http://bit.ly/hyhlXq
Lol the meat is organic #lmao RT @BibiNetAlKole: RT @Fafane06: As per @fufujr there's something called organic ... http://tmi.me/86hMD
RT @CMAResources I don't think every church should be organic, I think every church is organic...or it's not the true church - @Neil_Cole
I don't think every church should be organic, I think every church is organic...or it's not the true church - @Neil_Cole #organicchurch
Pure Foods: Organic and Pure Foods http://t.co/7xGe0Om vía @Digg
"People. Colors. Apps. Cats. Bacon. Organic. Bieber. Mobile. Social. Local. Pivot" Lulz. http://t.co/zYzJTJM
Ew organic yogurt looks so nasty. But oh it's so good! http://t.co/tjS4GLU
Word RT @SelfishMom: ... I will not be needing the flyer 4 the camp w/organic vegan snacks. I don't need to be judged all summer.
I tried to give organic a chance but some of my 'organic' carrot sticks for lunch tasted like grass. Back to regular ones next time around..
Organic Church Principles in the Conventional Church by Phil Helfer | Free Audio- Listen or Download http://ow.ly/4jiQU
RT @HEALEO: DRINK SPECIAL- 50% off MATCHA LATTE all day. Organic grade A matcha & milk of choice (I recommend hemp) http://fb.me/uGxQVNlU
@sciamannata full-fat organic, don't hold with artificially enriched. (I know what I'm doing! anyway skim milk has no taste)
Dr. Lab's Tipsters Using Organic Materials in Analogue Lifestyle in Magazine - Lomography http://t.co/QCLWXTB via @lomography
lol lol hella strong in the drinks I had I don't think it mixes well RT @LLzors Ok so that organic vodka last night was gross
RT @CMAResources: Interview on Organic Leadership with @Neil_Cole http://ow.ly/4eb02 on @GottaLife Radio
Malta Organic Agriculture Movement (MOAM) http://fb.me/CIkRlXhw
Improve your organic web rankings by having a look at the #SEO Tools that will help: - http://t.co/VLmO9fr - @MarketingB2B
Interview on Organic Leadership with @Neil_Cole http://ow.ly/4eb02 on @GottaLife Radio
@leejunlin omg dude you are obsessed with farms leh! got organic crops? my father grows organic fruits in his gdn HAHAA.
RT @gottalife: Sow a church, reap an institution. Sow the gospel, reap a church. Join Organic Church Today http://www.organicchurchtoday.com
@sarah_m_davies in my case, it's mostly biology, often organic chemistry :l
@priyamooky awesome article Priya! I gave up my med school dreams after organic chem!!
Hey organic cupcake makers, how about you stop telling me your ingredients are organic. I don't give a shit, just make it taste good.
@thefattony diet may slow it, no salt, no sugar at all, organic rice,cottage, cheese, veges all salt sugar free, we did it for ours.
Jason: "Embraceable You" (Nat King Cole) -- He has a voice like a new version organic soy milk. You know, silk.
@LoveAmrita @XOXOsukanya Try Physicians Formula: Organic wear® 100% Natural Origin Mascara. Organic stuff won't give you the itchies.
@CoolDadBro organic basil
@bluerumm it is! We have totally switched over to organic. We drink too much milk to do it totally bottled, but I wanted some good cream.
@mikaylacarson wow I'm impressed. Is that harmony organic milk? We buy bottled milk as well. It's the best!
@_finn i do so organic efficiencies changing quite a bit - just a bit of initial push i think is needed, and challenge once in a while :)
@mikaylacarson hey you should try an organic fruits and veggies delivery service. It forces you to center your meals around the produce
@biz_analyst_AD @OmnitureCare Correct, as organic search is based on: referrer=search engine, no tracking code and presence of a search term
@OmnitureCare Frm Google I click on our Organic SEO site lnk (kia.com). We overwrite referrer w/ 'kia.com'--we losing Orgnic Search credit?
RT @cmaresources: How to Explain Simple/Organic Church in 2 Minutes on a N... http://youtu.be/dyMQl7sPKMY?a //Would you agree with this?
RT @CMAResources: RT @roytmcclung: How to Explain Simple/Organic Church on a Napkin in 2 Minutes... http://ff.im/z7yIm
@adellmcc Cashew butter, A'Dell! ORGANIC cashew butter!
Organic or Conventional - Check out these lists of foods http://bit.ly/fnmOjA
@impeus I would say you could use that organic shea I gave you, but the thing with shea is it absorbs so quickly... might not be any good.
A list of 15 foods that you can buy that do not have to be produced organically (Just Posted) http://j.mp/fnmOjA #food #organic
@natejtaylor Organic must be the topic today. Check out our blog http://j.mp/fnmOjA #organic #food
Not sure how to respond to this. RT @guykawasaki Breastmilk ice cream: Taking organic to a whole new level - Holy Kaw! http://bit.ly/hQFMSC
RT @delortae: USDA uncovers scheme to import fake Chinese organic food http://ow.ly/42e74 #china #food #counterfeit
RT @CMAResources: Stories of Going Organic for Conventional Churches - Workshop Part 1 | http://ow.ly/41UUC #organicchurch
Tonight's dinner: dad's hunting spoils - venison 'tenderloin' roast I marinated overnight - and organic green peas. Yum!
@betaCooking find a 'normal' organic yogurt brand and put about 2-3 cups in a cheesecloth and let the liquid drain through for a few hours.
Check out the @giggle Better Basics Organic Crib Sheet in this stunning nursery featured in coochicoos! http://bit.ly/frQJiv
For the record, I only use certified organic free-range pixels.
@giggle Organic boppy pillow and bath towels.
Organic SEO - 4 Ways to Achieve Traffic Organically - Or Naturally http://ht.ly/3VxGk
@ekgarcia just wondering how your organic chemistry class is going?
Dinner before exercise ... (at Waraporn Salapao | วราภรณ์ ซาลาเปา Q.House Lumpini) — http://t.co/LDR975wF
VOA Radio: While #ROK signals desire for new #DPRK talks, US says Beijing should tell Pyongyang to exercise restraint. http://t.co/S2tcKOut
@corq 10150u and 14480u buzzing with exercise type tfc. lotsa players, lotsa tfc. Adjusting tinfoil hat now because of proximity to 11-9-11
@alohaglide Yeah, that's what I was anticipating. Feels like a kind of zen exercise.
It's better to BE #Happy than APPEAR to be HAPPY #Writing#exercise#cooking #singing#playingkeys#painting#gardening brings me great happiness
Definitely gonna exercise tomorrow! :-)
Here's another easy-peasy fun and breezy exercise to try: writerly people-watching-- http://bit.ly/gwXr0p
This blogpost is an exercise to figure out what age group you should be writing for. http://bit.ly/hC182s
Same here RT @ladylelomajozi: I hate it when they're cute boys at the gym! I can't exercise properly.. I need to find a women only gym asap!
How does #exercise help improve #heart health? It preserves and builds #muscle strength! Read more from @LATimesHealth http://lat.ms/epiREs
@HospitalTea Isn't that a form of exercise?
"Continue to ask difficult questions, explore unpopular lines of thought and exercise your academic freedom" - @Biddy_Martin
Chancellor @Biddy_Martin response on open records, @wcronon: "Exercise your academic freedom." http://bit.ly/eD6NLf #cronon
RT @UWMadison: Chancellor @Biddy_Martin response on open records, @wcronon: "Exercise your academic freedom." http://bit.ly/eD6NLf
RT @UWMadison: Chancellor @Biddy_Martin response on open records, @wcronon: "Exercise your academic freedom." http://bit.ly/eD6NLf #cronon
RT @uwmadison: Chancellor @Biddy_Martin response on open records, @wcronon: "Exercise your academic freedom." http://bit.ly/eD6NLf #cronon
Chancellor @Biddy_Martin response on open records, @wcronon: "Exercise your academic freedom." http://bit.ly/eD6NLf #cronon
Chancellor @Biddy_Martin response on open records, @wcronon: "Exercise your academic freedom." http://bit.ly/eD6NLf #cronon
@johnalewis I think I smell a new exercise fad
This is going to change email writing forever. And how I get my daily exercise. http://hcok.im/4Kx8 #googleaprilfools
@kevinkane37 I liked getting the chance to get some exercise all together last week.
completed his food and exercise diary for 03/29/2011 and was under his calorie goal #myfitnesspal
RT @SelfishMom: @kmohara Think the answer is for me to hire someone to open my packages for me.> Wise. Hmm. Who can exercise for me?
Save the Chilren Fund is not a medical charity, Orphanage or sweetie distrubution exercise
Daily exercise: climbing up and down 6 storeys worth of stairs
Can Transport Managers’ exercise continuous and effective control http://bit.ly/e5WKw6
@sarahkatenorman what's green exercise?
Scientists are inventing a pill that makes your brain think exercise is fun, but it's not cheeseburger flavour yet. Hang in there America.
فشولي خلقي شوي صورة بشار تتعرض الى "صرامي http://me.lt/3TXHc Near #Deraa, ppl exercise their freedom of expression #Syria v @Tharwacolamus
Those who think they have not time for bodily exercise will sooner or later have to find time for illness. -Edward Stanley
@serialinsomniac It's definitely gov legislation. You'll have had one but not been shown it-they're generally just a tick-box exercise... ->
@DrMichellexo Truthfully, it is the ONLY reason to exercise. Or so I've heard. ;)
Today's daily exercise.. really making productive use of my time in this 67-205 lecture. http://bit.ly/eJZJ49
@NauvalYzd hmm... You said exercise earlier. So if I'm doin sit up on my bed, it is still an exercise, right?
@jazgar I went thru similar exercise, not GOP fascist but that they are not telling truth lying, hidden agenda etc. under #GOPExposed
Goal 4 next week: 6 days of exercise #noexcuses
Almost killed a cat (Ava) closing the door, tried to put on my exercise pants instead of a sweater. Maybe I should go back to bed.
@TauxFu the same exercise of arbitrary discretion got WL dumped in december.
@BillsArcaneSide because you'll lemme exercise it on you e.o
Avisados estamosOut of shape? Intense exercise, sex may raise heart risk http://t.co/6cfLfOe via @ziteapp
#Spring is in the air! @DaculaPatch shares some great #cooking & #exercise tips to keep your heart healthy this Spring http://bit.ly/hKUS8V
@brasonja Have a diligent day as well ;) Time to get some exercise here, cracking on all sides. so #TYL :)) @photoasia
@NiGhT_RaVeN13 "I prefer physics not medical." and "I font exercise are not tips lol
Working that tarp might be a good weight loss exercise too! RT @TheWrigleyBlog: Why can't they just option Carlos Silva to the Grounds Crew?
Bummer: Heart risk spikes after sex, exercise http://feedly.com/k/gdIkwD
Buckle up. Looks like we'll exercise democracy soon enough.
83. I love walking for exercise. #100factsaboutme
completed her food and exercise diary for 03/20/2011 and was under her calorie goal #myfitnesspal
I think I need a rule like if I can't get exercise in I can only eat fruit. Or nothing.
Ok, I am gonna take another pain pill then try to do more exercise. I need to stay mobile.
Well exercise was a mistake. Just worsened the #endo pain.
@alvinng my philosophy is eat first exercise later
Moss is Boss – An Exercise in Observation - http://ow.ly/4h2r0 #photography via @_Fleur__ / RT @photoasia
Dinner for Schmucks is a painful exercise in comedy, yet I can't look away.
@respectthebeard Are we back on for exercise on Sunday? Or will your irritable bowels have the last word on that?
RT @photoasia: Moss is Boss – An Exercise in Observation - http://ow.ly/4h2r0 #photography via @_Fleur__
@alvinng must exercise more!
. @genegeek It'd be me writing. Nice exercise to cover same story in diff ways, slightly diff style, maybe reach diff audience
whatever happened to those exercise bikes with the pedal-powered fans? i know those are way retro, but for once they had the right idea.
@electropura I used to get them. Either: not eating enough, too much caffeine, not enough exercise or YOU'RE DYING. Probs not the last one.